Imagine a place where nothing is impossible.
Tomorrowland is a adventure, family, mystery film directed by Brad Bird.
Bound by a shared destiny, a bright, optimistic teen bursting with scientific curiosity and a former boy-genius inventor jaded by disillusionment embark on a
danger-filled mission to unearth the secrets of an enigmatic place somewhere in time and space that exists in their collective memory as "Tomorrowland."
Casey Newton, played by Britt Robertson.
Frank Walker, played by George Clooney.
Athena, played by Raffey Cassidy.
David Nix, played by Hugh Laurie.
Eddie Newton, played by Tim McGraw.
Frank's Dad, played by Chris Bauer.
Tomorrowland is a 2015 American science fiction film directed by Brad
Bird with a screenplay by Bird and Damon Lindelof.
The film is based on the themed land Tomorrowland from the Disney
Parks and a story by Bird, Lindelof, and Jeff Jensen.
It stars George Clooney, Hugh Laurie, Britt Robertson, Raffey
Cassidy, Tim McGraw, Kathryn Hahn, and Keegan-Michael Key.
In the film, a disillusioned genius inventor and a teenage science enthusiast embark to an intriguing
alternate dimension known as "Tomorrowland", where their actions directly affect their own world.
Walt Disney Pictures originally announced the film in June 2011 under the working title
1952 and later retitled it to Tomorrowland after the Disney Parks theme land.
In drafting their story, Bird and Lindelof took inspiration from the progressive cultural movements of the Space Age, as well as Walt
Disney's optimistic philosophy of the future, notably his conceptual vision for the planned community known as EPCOT.
Principal photography began in August 2013, with scenes
shot at multiple locales in five countries.
Tomorrowland was released by Walt Disney Studios Motion Pictures
in conventional and IMAX formats on May 22, 2015.
The film, which received mixed reviews from critics, grossed $209 million worldwide and was
considered a commercial failure for losing Disney $120–150 million at the box office.
The film explores themes of inventor, apocalypse,
destiny, dreamer, futuristic car.
The tone is uplifting and thought_provoking and mind_bending.